I think familiarity.
Is is a quite an interesting concept when we think about
organizations and structures.
And they were big. Part of that is really some of the ideas
around.
Hiring in one's own image.
And part of that is.
We look at these kind of workspaces and they're microcosm
of society.
And very often it depends what that society is to the
individuals that may be the the power brokers or the
stakeholders in that organization. Now if those individuals
are exposed to diverse ranges of people that in a sense
prick something in one's conscience to think about how
useful a diverse workforce be.
If individuals aren't exposed to that, and by proxy their
world is quite narrow in that sense, it can limit the range
of people that they bring into those organizations, which
is why you can have these homogeneous organizations which
have, you know, which are predominantly white if we're
talking about huge executive companies. And in terms of
thinking about that opportunity, it tends to often be
reactive in response to a particular phenomena. So let's
take the most recent.
Vintage.
Black Lives Matter movement in 2020.
There was a huge kind of.
Rear guard action and response by organisations to think
about how they diversify things. But what's been
interesting about that?
Is we're kind of four years away from that.
And actually a lot of those organizations have slip back
into patterns of replicating that familiarity in terms of
the types of people they have in those organizations.